Alright, Beck, let's make
this really interesting, okay?
Whoever burps
their baby the fastest
gets out of diaper duty
for the whole entire day.
What do you say?
You're on, pal,
because I have Alex.
And, let's face it,
he is the king of gas.
Yes, that may be true
but we want it more.
Right, Nicky?
See that? He's got
the eye of the Tiger.
Alright, ready?
And...burp 'em.
- Come on, Alex.
- Come on, Nicky.
- Come on.
What's going on?
Oh, we're having
a little contest to see
who could burp the fastest.
[burps]
I won. I'm still
the burp champion.
In your face.
[theme music]
♪ Ahhh ahh ahh ahhh ♪
♪ Aaah ♪
♪ What ever happened
to predictability ♪
♪ The milkman
the paperboy ♪
♪ Evenin' TV ♪
♪ When did I get
to livin' here ♪
♪ Somebody tell me please ♪
♪ This whole world's
confusing me ♪
♪ Clouds as mean as
you ever seen ♪
♪ Ain't a bird
who knows your tune ♪
♪ Then a little voice ♪
♪ Inside you whispers ♪
♪ Kid don't sell
your dreams so soon ♪
♪ Everywhere you look ♪
♪ Everywhere ♪
♪ There's a heart ♪
♪ A hand to hold on to ♪
♪ Everywhere you look ♪
♪ Everywhere ♪
♪ There's a face ♪
♪ Of somebody who needs you ♪
♪ Everywhere you look ♪
♪ When you're lost out there ♪
♪ And you're all alone ♪
♪ A light is waiting ♪
♪ To carry you home ♪
♪ Everywhere you look ♪
♪ Dooby do ba ba dow ♪♪
[instrumental music]
Okay, boys, this is your
first trip to Aunt Ida's.
And we're going
to have a good time.
'She's gonna hug you
and kiss you'
'and pinch your little cheeks
for about three hours.'
Alright, boys,
let's go out there
and make Channel 8 a winner.
Because we're lean.
We're mean.
And we're clean.
Honey, I've never actually
seen you on ice skates.
Um, do-do you know anything
at all about hockey?
I took the kids
to "Smurfs On Ice."
What's to know?
The point is,
the boys are back.
We're having a good time,
we're hanging out together.
- The boys.
- That's right.
Hanging out
just like the old days.
That's right.
One for all, all for one.
Just like the Three Musketeers.
- Athos.
- Porthos.
Annette.
Not Mouseketeers,
it's the Musketeers.
Guys, I have one question.
Why do I've to be the goalie?
Danny, come on.
Goalie is the safest
position on the ice.
Yeah? Then why am I wearing
200 pounds of foam rubber?
[doorbell ringing]
Joey, how fast are those
pucks going, anyway?
Not fast.
90-100 miles per hour.
Maybe, I should sit on the bench
and make you guys hot cocoa.
I got it, I think.
- Hey, Vicky.
- Hey.
Ooh! I can't wait to see
my co-host in action.
Really?
Guys, what are we waiting for?
Hot cocoa?
Let's get out on the ice!
Yeah, let me rub your bald
little heads for good luck.
Okay?
Beck, if they don't start
growing hair within a week
I'm buying them both
matching baby toupees.
Alright, here we go.
Okay, Deej, we're leavin'.
I'll be right out, Vicky.
Bye, dad, have fun at the game.
Try not to get hurt.
Hey, I can take care
of myself.
But, Deej, if anything
happens to me..
...I love you so much.
Thanks for giving up
a Saturday to babysit. Huh?
Oh, It's no problem.
I was supposed to go out
with Steve but he never called.
That's no big deal.
Okay, so he's a total hunk,
but it's no big deal..
Did I say that already?
'Cause it's no big deal.
Oh, and I want you to make sure
Stephanie finishes
her book report.
And I don't want
Michelle going outside
because she still has
her sniffles, okay?
Got it.
Thanks, Deej.
I owe you one.
You mean like
one red mustang convertible?
No, I mean like
one more big dad hug.
Come here.
- Hi, Stephanie.
- Hello, Michelle.
[sniffling]
Michelle, do you mind?
No.
Michelle, don't you have
anything better
to do than to sniffle
in my ear while I'm working?
Don't know where it comes from
but it just keeps coming.
[doorbell ringing]
(D.J.)
'I'll get it.'
- Steve, hi.
- Hi, back.
- You look great.
- Well, thanks.
Oh, it's nice to see you.
What are you doing here?
Didn't you get my note
about going to the movies?
I gave it to Maria to give to
Kimmy to give to you in home ec.
Oh, no wonder I didn't get it.
Kimmy always ditches home ec.
She says she's gonna marry
a doctor and get a maid.
- Hey, let's go to the movies.
- Great! We're out of here.
Wait. I'm not out of here.
I have to babysit.
Oh, too bad.
No, wait.
I can go.
- What about babysitting?
- Oh, yeah. Um..
That's no problem
because we'll take
my little sisters with us.
Your little sisters?
Oh! You'll love them.
They're adorable.
Wait till you see 'em.
Okay, we're going
to the movies.
Put on your coats
and act adorable.
I cannot leave
this house, dad said.
Dad's not here. I'm in charge.
That makes me dad.
Until the real dad comes back
and makes you grounded.
You don't get it.
The hottest guy in the junior
class is in our living room.
He has his own car.
And he can grow a mustache
in less than a month.
Are you sure
you wanna do this?
Oh sure. I'm sure.
Girls, come with me.
I'd like you to meet
a very good friend of mine.
Steve, these are my sisters,
Stephanie and Michelle.
Let's see you
grow a mustache.
Not that I don't trust you,
Steverino.
But..
...can I see
your driver's license?
- I told you they're adorable.
- Oh, we better get going.
"Thunder Raceway"
starts in a half hour.
"Thunder Raceway?"
I believe that's rated PG.
Parental guidance suggested?
No parents,
no guidance. No go.
Steph, give me a break.
The only G-rated movie out
is "The Littlest Sea Lion."
- I've been dying to see that.
- Yeah, me too.
I love when
the little sea lion goes..
[imitating sea lion]
- I'm really sorry about this.
- Hey, it's alright.
Hopefully, we won't even
be watching the movie.
Why not?
Okay, no more questions.
Everybody in the car.
I got the front seat!
Wanna hear something amazing?
Sure, kid.
[sniffling]
I told you they're adorable.
Okay, we got drinks,
popcorn, mints, licorice
chocolate raisins,
and of course bonbons.
You forgot the nachos.
Michelle, let's not be pigs.
Ah, Steph, where's my change?
Change? If there was any money
left I would have bought nachos.
Oh, Steph.
Excuse me, could you
save our place? Thanks.
Steve, this is really
embarrassing
but I don't have enough money
to pay for my sisters.
I only have enough for us.
Hey, maybe we should forget
the whole thing.
No, no, wait, um..
...why don't you
just buy our tickets?
Kimmy just started working here.
Maybe she'll have an idea.
That'll be a first.
- Thank you.
- Enjoy the show.
Don't spill anything.
I'm the one that
has to clean up!
Hey, Kimmy, we need to talk.
I know.
You're with Steve Peters.
So why'd you bring
those rug rats?
I had no choice.
Hey, can I borrow ten bucks?
Yeah, sure, but I can't
get it right now.
I'm on duty.
If I leave,
kids will sneak in.
Kimmy, that's the answer.
You have to sneak
my sisters in.
What? You're asking me
to commit a crime?
My first day on the job?
I'm shocked!
- You're not gonna do it?
- Well, of course I'll do it.
But I'm still shocked!
Thanks. You're my hero.
Thank you.
- Come on, Michelle.
- I got our tickets.
Great!
Thank you.
Enjoy the show.
You, too.
Go right on in.
Hold it.
Where's our stubs?
Uh! You don't need any.
Tell them, Kimmy.
Yeah, that's right,
because..
...you're
the one millionth customer.
I'm the one millionth
customer? Alright!
What do I win? A new car?
No, you win a free pass
for you and a guest.
Oh! Let's see.
Who should I take?
What are you,
nuts? Take me.
Come on.
Let's go. Keep the line moving.
Thank you.
- How's this?
- Perfect.
This is cozy.
It'll be even cozier
when you two move behind us.
Come on, right now.
Let's go.
Enjoy the little sea lion.
See you when it's over.
[instrumental music]
Alright, a Pink Panther cartoon!
♪ Da da da ♪
♪ Da da da da da da
da da da da ♪
Shh.
♪ Da da da da da ♪♪
I don't wanna hear a peep out of
you two until the movie is over.
- Peep.
I mean it.
(Stephanie)
'Watch this, Michelle.'
He's going to put
his arm around D.J.
He's getting
closer, closer--
D.J., watch out!
That's it. You two
in the back row, right now.
Come on, move it.
Move it. Move it.
How rude!
Now, where were we?
I think we were
right about here.
Excuse me, young ladies.
I'm sorry to bother you.
We've had some kids
switching theaters.
Could I check
your ticket stubs?
We don't need any.
I'm the one millionth customer.
And this is my guest,
one millionth and one.
You better come with me.
Come on, Michelle.
I'll bet we won a new car.
Oh! Sorry, I'll wait.
Smooch away.
Kimmy, what is it?
My manager just busted
your twerpy sisters.
He's taking them
into his office.
Oh, man, if he calls
my dad, I'm dead.
You're dead?
I could lose my job.
They better not squeal on me.
G-I-B-B-L-E-R.
Gibbler.
[instrumental music]
Now, why in the world
would Kimmy Gibbler
tell you that you're
the one millionth customer?
We've only been open a week.
Well, sir, I'm sorry
to have to tell you this
but...you've hired a nut case.
[sniffling]
Well, now, don't cry.
I'm not crying.
I got the sniffles.
That was a good one.
Here you are.
Girls,
I'm so disappointed in you.
Who are you?
I'm their sister, sir.
The good sister.
What scam
did they run this time?
The old one-millionth
customer story?
But Kimmy said that--
Shame on you.
Blaming sweet,
poor, innocent Kimmy.
Sir, they may look cute,
but don't be fooled.
They've been sneaking into
G-rated movies all over town.
In fact, they're known
as Snake and Sniffles.
Which one am I?
Well, I-I called your home
but no one answered.
Oh, that's too bad.
My father needs
to know about this.
But don't worry.
I'll make sure they get punished
like they've never
been punished before.
Snake, Sniffles, let's go.
I'm Sniffles?
Yes, you're Sniffles.
Oh, I get it.
That's because
I have the sniffles.
Good one.
Oh, sir.
One last thing.
The popcorn
could be a little fresher.
And stay out.
Alright, you two girls
have a seat.
Now, we're not out
of the woods yet.
We can't tell dad
what really happened.
So we've to tell him
what didn't happen.
You mean
you want us to lie to dad?
No, I don't want you to lie.
I just want you to tell a fib.
A tiny little fiblet.
Why? So you won't
get in trouble?
You didn't do your book report
so you're in trouble too.
Rats.
Am I in trouble like Snakes?
No, but one day you will be.
And Stephanie and I
will be there to bail you out.
So will you help us?
Let me think.
Alright, I'm in.
Now the secret to a good lie
uh, fiblet, is details.
Now, Steph, um, you worked
on your book report all day.
For lunch, you had a baloney
sandwich sliced diagonally
with a glass of chocolate milk
and a ho ho.
Could I have a ding dong
instead of a ho ho?
Whatever.
Now, Michelle when dad
asks you what you did today
you say...D.J. and I
played Candyland, and I won.
Can I have a ding dong, too?
What's with you kids
and ding dongs?
If Snakes get one, then
Sniffles should get one, too.
Okay, you get a ding dong
for winning Candyland.
Wow! I had a great day!
Are you sure this will work?
Oh, it can't miss.
As long as
we stick to our story.
Now, Michelle,
what did you do today?
Duh!
I went to the movies
with you and got in trouble.
We're doomed.
Michelle, you played
Candyland with me
and won a ding dong, remember?
Oh, yeah.
Can I take back my duh?
Now get off my case. So I wasn't
the best skater out there.
You call that skating?
Your butt never left the ice.
Even flat on my back,
I got some good shots off.
Yeah, you got the winning goal.
For the other team!
But the goalie
should've blocked that shot.
Or any shot.
Danny, what the heck
were you doing
on your hands and knees, anyway?
I was just cleaning
the slush around my area.
It's not an area,
it happens to be a goal crease
and you're supposed to be
defending it, not cleaning it!
I was defending it.
Until it got all icky.
Danny, you've got
a real problem--
Let me tell you something,
you've got a real problem.
You take this hockey stuff
way too seriously.
Hey, listen, Dippity-do Head.
What, Elmer Fudd Face?
Take that back, Do Head.
Make me, Fudd Face.
Hey, hey, hey, Do Head,
Fudd Face, come on.
Whatever happened
to the Three Musketeers?
Musketeer this, Mop and Glo.
It's Mr. Mop and Glo
to you, buddy.
Oh, c'mon, it's ridiculous
you out there cleanin' the ice.
Hey, I've seen players
cleaning the ice--
- I've seen--
- Not with pledge!
Okay, boys, you made it through
your first visit to Aunt Ida's.
And I promise, we'll get
all that lipstick off.
[indistinct chatter]
Here we go.
- I got that.
- Ow!
Stop it!
Hello, boys.
(in unison)
Hello.
We were just, uh,
horsing around a little.
That's right,
just three guys horsing around.
- Yep. It's a guy thing.
- Oh, isn't that cute?
Your daddy and his buddies
roughhousing like little boys.
Well, I guess
that's how you strengthen
those bonds of male friendship.
Just like those chimps
we saw last week at the zoo.
Becky's right.
- We're no better than chimps.
- Yeah.
What's wrestling around on the
carpeting going to prove anyhow?
Want to see who can
do the most pushups?
Yeah.
(in unison)
One, two, three, four.
[sniffling]
Get used to it.
Here comes dad.
Now, everybody
remember their stories.
Baloney sandwich,
book report.
Candyland, ding dong.
Hey, girls.
- Hello.
Deej, thanks again
for babysitting.
It's really great to know
that I have a mature
responsible daughter
that I can count on.
Thanks, dad.
(DJ)
I am scum. I'm lower than scum.
I'm the scum
they scrape off scum.
So, Steph, did you finish
your book report?
Sure did, and then I had
a baloney sandwich
diagonally sliced a refreshing
glass of chocolate milk
and a ding dong.
That sounds so fake.
Sounds like you had
a really productive day.
He bought it!
And how was your day, Michelle?
Let's see..
We're busted.
I played Candyland with D.J.,
and I won a ding dong.
Yes!
That's great.
You know what, honey?
Let me just get a tissue
and wipe your nose for you.
I've turned my sisters
into liars..
...but good liars.
I've got an idea.
Since you girls were cooped up
in the house all day.
Why don't we go
to a movie, tonight?
- Alright.
- Yeah.
Uh-oh. He knows something.
How about
"The Littlest Sea Lion?"
Have you girls seen it?
No, dad, I can honestly
say we haven't.
Great. You know, Deej?
Since you're becoming
so responsible
maybe it's time I raised
your allowance, huh?
I don't deserve a raise.
How does two-fifty more
a week sound?
Sounds great.
Why is he torturing me?
I love you, sweetheart.
I can't take it anymore!
Dad, Steve came over
and we took Stephanie
and Michelle to the movies.
We didn't have enough money
to pay for them.
So I made Kimmy sneak 'em in,
and then we all got caught.
And then I forced them to lie
to you about the whole thing.
And that's what really happened.
I feel so much better.
Ooh. That's a bad face.
I'm really sorry, dad.
So am I.
I can't believe this.
It's true. The whole thing
about the baloney sandwich?
Never happened.
Go ahead, dad. Ground me.
Alright, you're grounded.
All three of you.
We're all grounded?
Even me, your little princess?
Dad, they don't deserve it.
I told them they weren't lying
just telling a fiblet.
They still went along with it.
Ultimately,
you're each responsible
for that choices
that you made.
And you gonna have
to accept the consequences.
Huh?
That means you do the crime,
you do the time.
Does this mean no
Little Sea Lion?
No Little Sea Lion.
That's the second time
I missed him today!
Deej, what happened?
We got away with the whole
thing and then you blew it.
I couldn't go through with it.
Ever hear that little voice in
your head saying this is wrong?
Sure, but I told it to shut up
and I listened to you.
Do I have a little
voice in my head?
Yeah, everybody does.
It's called your conscience.
And when you do something
you know is wrong
your conscience reminds you
over and over and over..
...until you
do something about it.
It sounds like a pain
in the neck.
Look, I'm really sorry
I got you guys grounded.
Thanks for backing me up.
Tell you what, Steph.
I'm going to help you
with this book report.
And after that, Michelle
you and I are going
to play Candyland.
And I promise to spend
more time with both you guys.
Give me a hug.
Hey, you guys can hang out
in my room any time you want.
Whoa, DJ,
don't get carried away.
Here, let's start.
It's chapter 12.
♪ Ahhh ahh ahh ahhh ♪
[theme music]
♪ Dooby do ba ba dow ♪♪